

EDUCATION

JUN 2009 - JUN 2013

Secondary Education

Malangas Institute

JUN 2013 - JUN 2015

ACS

Western Mindanao State University

JUN 2015 - JUN 2017

BSCS

Western Mindanao State University

SKILLS

Computer Skills (Word, Excel, Access, File Management)

Photoshop/Illustrator/Figma

PHP/CodeIgniter/Laravel/Flight PHP

HTML5/CSS3/SASS

JavaScript/JQuery

Professional Skills: Designing Database (Гозоць, 17193ць), Developing Васк-Епа от Server Side System, Front-End or Client Side

NICK JAY BAGUIO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Phone: 0912-6675-199 | Email: b.nickjay05@gmail.com| Date of Birth: 1997-04-05

Address: Purok Bagong Lipunan, Malangas Zamboanga Sibugay, 7038

ABOUT ME

I am a Freelance Web Developer, Throughout the last 3 years, i have been building web based applications and engaged in a variety of freelance projects.

I aims to help business owners to develop their desired websites and implement advance functionality and responsiveness, I can help to make ideas come true and i don't ignore any challenges may have.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2012 - FEB 2013

Student Assistant

Arcer Computer Educational Development System

Brief Description: During my high school days, I've been part of the team that teaches other students and even elementary and secondary teachers in IT Related Course, Like: Word Processing, Spreadsheets, Vector Graphics, Photoshop and some basic concepts of programming.

JUN 2017 - APRIL 2018

Game Developer/Web Developer

www.tantraeternal.com

Brief Description: After i graduated on college, i established my own private mmorpg server, i run the server together with my friends. Though the server game files was released by Hanbitsoft Inc. My skills on handling game servers have been enhanced (e.g. networking, security, game strategy, game website).

NOV 2017 – AUG 2018

Web Developer - Freelance

Upwork.com

Brief Description: While working with my Private MMORPG Server, i worked as freelance also in Upwork as a Web Developer. I accept client offered jobs for any specific task.

AUG 2018 - PRESENT

Full Stack Developer

198 Internet Services

Brief Description: We do eCommerce Stores with advance eCommerce Admin Features and other medium and small scale web projects.